Close

Help me look for content related to…

Search for:  Search

WEBINAR: _Are You Prepared for NIS2?_ on November 12, 2024 [Learn More](https://www.aeris.com/news-and-press/webinar-are-you-prepared-for-nis2/) 

Search

[

](https://www.aeris.com/)

                * [Connectivity ManagementReduce supply chain costs, operational complexities, and bring your devices to market rapidly.](https://www.aeris.com/aeris-intelligent-iot-network/connectivity-management/)
                * [Security ManagementPrevent business disaster and operational issues by deploying Aeris’ state-of-the-art security controls.](https://www.aeris.com/aeris-intelligent-iot-network/security-management/)
                * [Performance ManagementStay focused on delivering better experiences and IoT applications to scale offerings globally.](https://www.aeris.com/aeris-intelligent-iot-network/performance-management/)
                * [Support ManagementGet the most from your IoT program with customized support services for all phases.](https://www.aeris.com/aeris-intelligent-iot-network/support-management/)
        
                * [Device ManagementExecute remote operations in less than 5 seconds.](https://www.aeris.com/aeris-mobility-suite/device-management-platform/)
                * [Service ManagementBuild. Deliver. Administer faster and more efficiently.](https://www.aeris.com/aeris-mobility-suite/service-platform/)
                * [Mobility EcosystemsReduce deployment time for new auto-grade applications by 70%.](https://www.aeris.com/aeris-mobility-suite/mobility-application-platform/)
                * [AnalyticsAccelerate your vehicle data collection, normalization, analysis and exposure with Aeris Mobility Suite.](https://www.aeris.com/aeris-mobility-suite/analytics/)
                * [Launching New IoT ProgramsEnsure a smooth launch with IoT expert program support.](https://www.aeris.com/why-aeris/launching-new-iot-programs/)
                * [Transitioning to LTE-MTake your next step to new connectivity technologies.](https://www.aeris.com/why-aeris/transitioning-to-lte-m/)
                * [Replacing 2G/3G TechnologiesEnhance the future of your business and eliminate 2G/3G.](https://www.aeris.com/why-aeris/replacing-2g-3g-technologies/)
                * [Improving an Existing IoT ProgramMake a great program even better with best-in-class connectivity.](https://www.aeris.com/why-aeris/improving-an-existing-iot-program/)
                * [Connected VehiclesDrive a connected vehicle program with the Aeris Mobility Suite.](https://www.aeris.com/why-aeris/connected-vehicles/)
    * * * [Leadership TeamMeet the IoT experts guiding business clients into the future.](https://www.aeris.com/about-aeris/#mgmtteam)
            * [LocationsWe specialize in excellence and intelligence around the globe.](https://www.aeris.com/about-aeris/locations/)
        * * [IoT For GoodWe’re committed to designing IoT programs that change the world.](https://www.aeris.com/iot-for-good/)

Search for:  Search

* [Secure IoT Platforms](https://www.aeris.com/iot/ "Secure IoT Platforms")Expand Sub LinksCollapse Sub Links
    * [Secure IoT Platforms](https://www.aeris.com/iot/ "Secure IoT Platforms")Expand Sub LinksCollapse Sub Links
    * [Industries](https://www.aeris.com/industries/ "Industries")Expand Sub LinksCollapse Sub Links
* [Connected Vehicles](https://www.aeris.com/aeris-mobility-suite/ "Connected Vehicles")Expand Sub LinksCollapse Sub Links
    * [Connected Vehicles](https://www.aeris.com/aeris-mobility-suite/ "Connected Vehicles")Expand Sub LinksCollapse Sub Links
* [Why Aeris?](# "Why Aeris?")Expand Sub LinksCollapse Sub Links
    * [Technology Expertise](# "Technology Expertise")Expand Sub LinksCollapse Sub Links
    * [Initiatives](# "Initiatives")Expand Sub LinksCollapse Sub Links
* [About Us](https://www.aeris.com/about-aeris/ "About Us")Expand Sub LinksCollapse Sub Links

Legal

Privacy Policy
==============

**Effective August 1st, 2021** In this Privacy Policy, we, Aeris Communications, Inc. (“Aeris”), along with our affiliates and subsidiaries under common ownership and control (the “Aeris group”), let you know the types of information we collect via [www.aeris.com](https://www.aeris.com/) and other web and mobile sites that link to this Privacy Policy, and how we use, store or share this information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we process as a data processor or service provider on behalf of our corporate customers. For example, we may, on behalf of our corporate customers (such as in connection with AerTrak mobile app), collect information associated with vehicles owned or operated by our corporate customers, including vehicle location and drivers associated with such vehicles. Aeris does not control how our corporate customers use information Aeris processes on their behalf, and you should consult with the applicable corporate customer to understand how they use the information they receive from Aeris. California consumers can view supplemental disclosures required under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) [here](https://www.aeris.com/privacy-policy/#california). Let us know if you have any questions by writing to [privacy@aeris.net](mailto:privacy@aeris.net). If you are located in the European Economic Area or the United Kingdom, please note that Aeris Communications, Inc., located at 2099 Gateway Place, Suite 600, San Jose, CA 95110, is the data controller of your information. **What Information do we collect or process?** We collect and process different types of data and information. Here are the types of information we collect:

* _Marketing prospects_. If you visit our websites, sign up for a webinar or express an interest in our products and services, we would like to know what your needs or interests are, and how to contact you. We may ask for information such as your name, job title, the company you represent, contact information including email address and phone number, your communication preferences, information about your business, and your interests in the Internet of Things.
* _From Aeris customers and users._ If you sign up for our products or services, we will ask you for information to set up and maintain your account, such as contact information of authorized account representatives. We may also ask you to go to a payment partner’s website to provide payment information. We do not retain any payment card information; please review the privacy notices at payment partner websites to understand how they process your information. When we process payments, we will receive information from our payment partners about the transaction; this could include small amounts of identifiable data. To provide services to you and your devices, we also need to gather other information relevant to the products or services we’re being asked to provide, including information about devices and applications that use our services.
* _For support purposes_. If you send a support request, either directly with us or through a company from which you purchase products or services, we collect contact information as described above, and information about the issues you are experiencing, such as information about the device, product and/or application you are using, the nature of the problem, and information about the circumstances in which the problem occurred, including location and time. We use this information to troubleshoot the problem and, if applicable, notify you of the status of the incident.
* _From Devices_. When you interact with us at a website or through a mobile app, we log and store certain types of information (“log data”). We also collect data from customer devices (“device data”) in the course of providing connectivity or other services to our customers.
    * _Log Data._ We may log your actions when you interact with our website, such as when you consent to collection of data, accept terms of use or other legal agreements, or manage your account or devices. We may also collect your IP address, data about your computer or mobile device, data relating to your search activity, the browser or operating system you use, the domain name of your Internet service provider, the pages you visit, or how long you remain at any website. If you have an account with us or our customer, we will collect your user ID and log the actions you take.
    * _Device Data_. In order to provide our services to customers and their devices, we collect a great deal of information, including device IDs, time stamps, authentication records, location information, carrier service used, signal strength, the origin, destination, type and quantity of traffic passed and other operational data. “Device” means any modem, radio, telephone, monitor or sensor, or other hardware or virtual device that contains a physical or virtual SIM card supplied or approved by Aeris for use of Aeris Services.
    * _Application Data_. When Aeris application services are used, we record what was used, the user and/or device using the service, actions taken in our mobile app (including any user content submitted to the mobile app) and log and device data as described above. For example, when anyone uses a mobile application to access AerTrak or connected vehicle services, we will collect the identity of the user (and, if applicable, mobile device), the vehicle being tracked or managed, and the type of action (e.g., view device location, or perform a remote door unlock). Application data also includes telemetry data, such as the performance of our application, diagnostics information, and changes in application settings made by the user and/or device.
    * _Contents of Device Traffic_. The actual contents of any SMS, data or voice transmissions made by customer Devices to customer-controller servers sent over the cellular network services provided by Aeris are not accessed, viewed or stored by Aeris. Transmissions made over cellular networks are made using standards-based security processes applicable to all cellular operators. Transmissions over other wireless networks are subject to the security processes put in place by the network operator or any encryption protocols arranged by the customer. If we enable emergency services or arrange call center services for a customer, we may be directed to record some calls made.
* _Community Forum Data_. We may sponsor a community forum or similar site to help customers and Aeris personnel communicate about issues of common interest. If you post to such a site, we may retain the content of posts as well as log data described above. You are encouraged to limit the amount of data you provide in your posts since they are publicly viewable.
* _Data Relevant to Employment_. If you apply for a position with any Aeris company, we and our third-party service providers will collect information you provide in connection with your application, including contact data and other information such as education and employment history, together with information we create or request as we evaluate your candidacy including, if applicable, reference and background checks. If you join us, we will of course need to process other information relevant to your work with us and issue a separate privacy notice then.

**For what purposes do we use your information?** We use your information to provide, support, develop and improve the products and services we offer to our customers and users. Here are examples of how we may use your information:

* _Provide, troubleshoot, and improve our products and services_. We use your information to provide our products and services to our customers and their users. This includes analyzing performance, troubleshooting errors, and improving effectiveness and user experience of our products and services. We also use your information to diagnose problems with devices that are using our services.
* _Provide and improve our operations_. We use your information to provide and improve our customer support and network operations.
* _Purchase our products and services_. We use your information to bill for services and process payments.
* _Improve user experience_. We use your information to understand how users interact with our websites and mobile apps, and how the websites and mobile apps are functioning, and in turn, improve user experience in these interactions. This includes customizing your interaction with our websites according to your customer status and interests.
* _Create new products and services_. We may use your information to create and new products and services.
* We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers, or other information we think you may find interesting using the email address you have provided, in accordance with applicable legal requirements. You can opt out of receiving these communications by following the unsubscribe instructions in the email. Please note that it may take some time for us to process your request, and you will still receive transactional communications from us that are non-commercial in nature.
* _Analytics_. We use your information for analytics purposes to maintain and improve our services, and determine if there is information that may be useful to us or our customers or partners. We may also aggregate information in a form that does not permit identification of specific individuals. In some circumstances, we may also de-identify information so that it can no longer identify you personally (“de-identified information). In addition to our internal use, we may share de-identified or aggregated information with third parties who use it for such purposes as industry analysis and demographic profiling. We take reasonable steps to prevent re-identification of any de-identified information, including prohibiting our personnel or service providers from re-identifying such information.
* _Communicate with you._ We use your information to communicate with you in relation to our products and services via different channels (i.e. by phone, email, chat). We may also contact you for customer service or market research purposes.
* _Comply with legal obligations_. We collect and use your information to comply with laws.
* _Fraud prevention_. We use your information to prevent, detect, and investigate fraud, abuse, illegal activities and violations of our terms of use and other policies.

**On which legal bases do we process your information?** We use your information based on the following legal bases:

* Where use of your information is necessary to perform our obligations under a contract with you (for example, to comply with our terms of service and/or to provide services).
* Where use of your information is necessary for our legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of others (for example, to provide security for our websites, products, software, or applications; operate our business and our services; make and receive payments; comply with legal requirements and defend our legal rights; prevent fraud and to know the customer to whom we are providing services).
* Where we have your consent, in accordance with applicable legal requirements, to use your information for a particular purpose.
* Where we use your information to comply with applicable legal obligations (for example, for tax and auditing purposes).

**What is our policy regarding cookies?** We use different kinds of “cookies” to collect information about your visits to the Aeris Sites or use of Internet-based services and applications. We use “persistent” cookies, small files stored on your hard drive, to make your future visits to Aeris websites more productive, such as by remembering some of your login information and your preferences. We also use “session-based” cookies that collect other log data as described above to help us analyze data about webpage traffic and to improve the Aeris websites. Session cookies are deleted when you close your browser window. We also use cookies for re-targeting purposes. You can block cookies completely or adjust how your browser handles cookies, although blocking cookies may make your use of some features of Aeris websites or web-based services less efficient. We may also use web beacons, pixels, tags or scripts in order to count visits, evaluate usage and effectiveness of campaigns and the like. We do not currently respond to “do not track signals” or similar mechanisms in web browsers. **With whom do we share your information?**

* _Service providers_. We store information with or allow access to your information to affiliated and unaffiliated service providers that support our business, including with website maintenance, database and cloud, customer support, payment processing, or other services. Our contracts with these third-party service providers only allow use of your information to provide these services on our behalf. We review the security policies and practices of our third-party service providers as appropriate as part of our own efforts to maintain the security of your information.
* _Affiliates and subsidiaries_. We may share the information we collect within the Aeris group.
* _Employers and corporate customers_. If your employer or our corporate customer provides you access to Aeris products and/or services, we may share information relating to your use of such products and/or services with said employer or corporate customer.
* _Law enforcement, court orders, and protection of our rights_. We may disclose any of your information to government officials as necessary to comply with applicable laws and orders. If we receive a request to disclose any such information, we may do so if we believe in good faith that such request is lawful and that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply. We may also disclose your information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
* _Other Disclosures_. We may also disclose your information if we believe it is necessary in order to protect our property rights or rights of a third party, to protect the safety of any person or of the public, or to prevent any activity that we believe is harmful, illegal or unethical. For example, we may need to use information in order to enforce our terms of service with customers and our workplace rules, or to engage in other business or corporate transactions. We will put in place appropriate security measures, such as non-disclosure agreements, whenever possible. In addition to our internal use, we may share de-identified or aggregated information with third parties who use it for such purposes as industry analysis and demographic profiling. Also, we may share your information in the context of mergers, acquisitions, divestitures and sales of all or some of our assets, in accordance with applicable law.

**How do we protect your information and where do we store it?**

* We use industry-standard measures to safeguard data, and have a continuous process in place to test the effectiveness of these measures and to review the threat landscape and new tools available. However, no Internet transmissions and no security measures can be completely secure. You have a role to play in security as well, and we ask that you use prudent measures to protect against unauthorized access to your account information, including logging out of your account when finished, not sharing your login information and taking other customary security precautions appropriate for the situation. The type of organizational or technical measures we use to secure our systems and information may differ depending on the sensitivity of the information and our assessment of how accidental or unauthorized disclosure or use of the information could threaten the rights and freedoms of natural persons.
* The Aeris group companies have entered into formal agreements based on standard clauses that commit us to follow the principles in the first part of this Privacy Policy when one Aeris company transfers certain information to another. When we use a third party to process your information, we require that they make similar promises to us, including agreeing not to process any information except as we have agreed with them.
* We are aware that there are people who may pose as legitimate businesses and try to trick you into disclosing information that can be used to steal your identity. We will not request your account login or password, your credit card information or any sensitive data that could be used to steal your identity, such as national identifying numbers, or gain access to your account in an unsolicited or non-secure email or telephone call. If you believe that someone representing themselves as being associated with Aeris has requested this information in a contact that you did not request or initiate, please contact us immediately at [security@aeris.net](mailto:security@aeris.net)so that we may verify the identity of the person contacting you and the validity of the request.

**Information for International Users**

### 1\. YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS

Depending on your location, your local laws may permit you to request that we:

* provide access to and/or a copy of certain information we hold about you;
* prevent the processing of your information for direct-marketing purposes (including any direct marketing processing based on profiling);
* update or rectify information which is out of date or incorrect;
* delete certain information which we are holding about you;
* oppose, cancel, or restrict the way that we process and disclose certain information;
* transfer your information to a third-party provider of services; and/or
* revoke your consent for the processing of your information

We will consider all requests and provide our response within the time period stated by applicable law. Please note, however, that certain information may be exempt from such requests in some circumstances, which may include if we need to keep processing your information for our legitimate interests or to comply with a legal obligation. We may request you provide us with information necessary to confirm your identity before responding to your request as required or permitted by applicable law.  To submit a request, please contact us using the Contact Information listed below.

### 2\. DATA TRANSFERS

Please note that in providing services to you, we may subcontract the processing of your information to, or otherwise share your information with, other members within the Aeris group, trusted service providers, and trusted business partners in countries other than your country of residence, including the United States, in accordance with applicable law. Such third parties may be engaged in, among other things, the provision of services to you, the processing of transactions and/or the provision of support services. By providing us with your information, you acknowledge any such transfer, storage or use. If you live in the EEA or the United Kingdom, please note that if we provide any information about you to any non-EEA or UK members of our group or third-party information processors, we will take appropriate measures to ensure such companies protect your information adequately in accordance with this Privacy Policy. These measures include signing Standard Contractual Clauses in accordance with EU and other data protection laws to govern the transfers of such data.

If applicable, you may make a complaint to the data protection supervisory authority in the country where you are based. Alternatively, you may seek a remedy through local courts if you believe your rights have been breached.

**Privacy Information for California Users** If you are a California resident, California law requires us to provide you with some additional information regarding your rights with respect to your “personal information” (as defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”)). _The personal information we collect, and how we use and share it._ The types of personal information we collect from and about you are summarized in the following chart:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Category** | **Examples** |
| **Identifiers** | A real name, unique personal identifier, online identifier, postal address, email address, account name, or other similar identifiers. |
| **Personal information categories listed in the California Consumer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e))** | A name, signature, telephone number, education, or medical information. Some personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories |
| **Commercial information** | Records of products or services purchased, obtained or considered. |
| **Internet or other similar network activity** | Browsing history, search history, information on a consumer’s interaction with a website, application, or advertisement. |
| **Geolocation data** | Physical location or movements. |
| **Professional or employment-related information** | Current or past job history or performance evaluations. |

For detailed information about how we use and share such personal information, please see the “For what purposes do we use your information,” and “With whom do we share your information” sections above in this Privacy Policy._California Rights_ If you are a California resident, the CCPA allows you to make certain requests about your personal information. Specifically, the CCPA allows you to request us to:

* Inform you about the categories of personal information we collect or disclose about you; the categories of sources of such information; the business or commercial purpose for collecting your personal information; and the categories of third parties with whom we share/disclose personal information.
* Provide access to and/or a copy of certain personal information we hold about you.
* Delete certain personal information we have about you.
* Provide you with information about the financial incentives that we offer to you, if any.

The CCPA further provides you with the right to not be discriminated against (as provided for in applicable law) for exercising your access, deletion, or sale opt out rights. Please note that certain information may be exempt from such requests under California law. For example, we need certain information in order to provide the services to you.  We will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before responding to a request, which may include, at a minimum, depending on the sensitivity of the information you are requesting and the type of request you are making, verifying your name and email address. To exercise your privacy rights described above, please submit a request to us via email at [CCPA@aeris.net](mailto:CCPA@aeris.net) or by using the Contact Information provided below. Please note that the CCPA sets forth certain obligations for businesses that “sell” personal information to third parties. We do not engage in such activity and have not engaged in such activity in the past twelve months from the effective date of this Privacy Policy. _California “Shine the Light” Disclosure_ The California “Shine the Light” law gives residents of California the right under certain circumstances to opt out of the sharing of certain categories of personal information (as defined in the Shine the Light law) with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not share your personal information with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes.   **Privacy information for Nevada Residents** Under Nevada law, Nevada residents who have purchased goods or services from us may opt out of the “sale” of “covered information” (as such terms are defined under Nevada law). “Covered information” includes, among other things, first and last name, address, email address, and phone number. If you are a Nevada resident who has purchased goods or services from us, you may submit a request to opt out of any future sales under Nevada law by contacting us using the contact information provided below. Please note we may take reasonable steps to verify your identity and the authenticity of the request. **How long do we keep information?** We and our third-party processors will keep information for as long as it is required for providing services to you or a customer, or we have another business purpose to do so (such as, but not limited to, business, tax, or legal purposes). When it is no longer needed for these purposes, we may retain it for no longer than is permitted by law or required by our records retention policy, and that period of retention is subject to our review and alteration. We may also delete it, or we may de-identify it and move it to another database for use in analytics. We may also keep copies in secure backup archives that are isolated from active production systems until deletion is appropriate. **Social media and links to other websites.**   The Aeris Sites may have social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, and widgets (such as for sharing a page) or interactive mini-programs. These features, which are hosted by third parties, may collect data similar to the log data mentioned earlier, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. The Aeris Sites may also include links to websites operated by third parties that we believe may be of interest or that are relevant to one of our services (such as an online app store for downloading a mobile app that interacts with our services). If you use any of these social media features, or visit sites using these links, you will leave our site, and you should note that we do not have any control over that other website and cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide while visiting such sites. Providing a link to third party websites does not mean that we endorse or warrant the products or services provided by any third parties and this Privacy Policy does not govern such sites. These third parties and the social media providers described earlier will have their own privacy policies that will govern the data they collect. **Contact Us.** If you have any concerns about the privacy practices of any Aeris group company, or would like to make any requests with respect to your information, please contact us at [privacy@aeris.net](mailto:privacy@aeris.net) or Aeris Communications, Inc., 2099 Gateway Place, Suite 600, San Jose, CA 95110, ATTN: General Counsel. In your message, please describe your concern, and we will try to resolve the issues. If you are a customer or end user of an Aeris customer, we will refer you to that customer to address your concerns. **Modification.** We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting an amended version at our home page at [www.aeris.com/privacy-policy/](https://www.aeris.com/privacy-policy/). You should check from time to time to see if we have updated this Privacy Policy. Your continued access and use of our services following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean you accept those changes.  If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you in accordance with our legal obligations.

Sign up to receive weekly roundups of the latest news and trends with IoT Connectivity.

Email Address(Required)

Email

This field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.

Δ

© 2024 Aeris.

Join Aeris Partner Network
--------------------------

First Name\*(Required)

Last Name\*(Required)

Company Name\*(Required)

Job Title\*(Required)

Business Email\*(Required)

Phone Number\*(Required)

Country\*(Required)

United StatesUnited KingdomCanadaIndiaAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBolivia, Plurinational State ofBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCongo, the Democratic Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCote d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and McDonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHungaryIcelandIndonesiaIran, Islamic Republic ofIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea, Democratic People's Republic ofKorea, Republic ofKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacaoMacedonia, the former Yugoslav Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMoldova, Republic ofMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorwayOmanPakistanPalestinePanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalQatarReunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint BarthélemySaint Helena, Ascension and Tristan da CunhaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Martin (French part)Saint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwanTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela, Bolivarian Republic ofVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishWallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwe

Message\*(Required)

Δ
